Hello? It looks like blood.
Did you even read the wikiHow link
I sent you on being goth?
No, I'm behind on my wiki reading.
(Raj:)I'm kind of on a John Grisham kick
right now.
(Howard:)-What?
-I finished reading The Pelican Brief...
(Raj:)...and loved it so much,
I dived right into The Client.
(Raj:)He was a lawyer himself, so his novels
are accurate as well as entertaining.
(Howard:)Just remember, we are lost boys.
Children of the night.
(Raj:)Great. Lost boys, children of the night.
Got it.
Can you pass the Chex Mix, please?
[HOWARD SIGHS]
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Howard:)We are lost boys.
(Girl:)Good for you.
I'm actually much more lost than he is.
(Girl:)Nice ink.
(Penny:)Thanks.
Can we buy you ladies a drink?
(Girl:)Two light beers.
Light beers. Well, wikiHow about that?